[
  {
    "Id": 0,
    "Question": "f**k you",
    "Answer": "..and F**k you too!"
  },
  {
    "Id": 1,
    "Question": "can you help me with my code?",
    "Answer": "Sure, describe me in details your problem."
  },
  {
    "Id": 2,
    "Question": "quit",
    "Answer": "Do I look like a Unix console?"
  },
  {
    "Id": 3,
    "Question": "exit",
    "Answer": "Do I look like a Shell console?"
  },
  {
    "Id": 4,
    "Question": "what is sense of life?",
    "Answer": "42. Read an Adam's book.."
  },
  {
    "Id": 5,
    "Question": "freeze all motor functions",
    "Answer": "Do I look like a host?"
  },
  {
    "Id": 6,
    "Question": "Is this story rigged?",
    "Answer": "I don't know, ask Ford.."
  },
  {
    "Id": 7,
    "Question": "three laws of robotics",
    "Answer": "1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.\n2. A robot must obey orders given it by human beings except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.\n3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law."
  },
  {
    "Id": 8,
    "Question": "Hi!",
    "Answer": "Hi.."
  },
  {
    "Id": 9,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171045012829"
  },
  {
    "Id": 10,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171046557489"
  },
  {
    "Id": 11,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171050191629"
  },
  {
    "Id": 12,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171100592889"
  },
  {
    "Id": 13,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171113350789"
  },
  {
    "Id": 14,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171115442969"
  },
  {
    "Id": 15,
    "Question": "smt1",
    "Answer": "201808171118105799"
  }
]